https://wssportfishing.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Warren Sellers Sportfishing
HomeSportfishing OptionsWarren’s Hosted Fishing VacationsCosta Rica Fishing ChartersAboutPhoto GalleryCosta Rica PhotosPanama PhotosTahiti PhotosGalapagos PhotosShopContact Select Page
Privacy PolicyWarren Sellers Sportfishing is committed to protecting your privacy. Any information Warren Sellers Sportfishing receives from you will never leave our private and secure servers. We will not use it for any purposes other than those which you have given your permission for. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties for their marketing and advertising purposes. We may amend this policy from time to time by updating this page.  Information We CollectWe use cookies as a way to enhance your experience on our website. Most web browsers are set up to accept cookies, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to de-activate cookies if you wish. The cookies include information about your IP address, your general location, the site from which you come, and the links followed when leaving Warren Sellers Sportfishing.Warren Sellers Sportfishing has a contact form as well as has an email link that you may use to contact us. We will use any information you provide only to respond to your inquiry. All electronic messages received from visitors are deleted when no longer needed.  Third-Party Websites and ApplicationsGoogle AnalyticsWarren Sellers Sportfishing uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to help analyze how individuals use websites they visit. Non-personal information generated by this cookie about your use of Warren Sellers Sportfishing is transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google does not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Google uses this information to understand how you use our site, and compiles reports on this activity to help us improve for our users. By using this site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google for these purposes. Links to External WebsitesVisitors are provided with the option to navigate to external websites. When a visitor selects the option to view the content from these websites, they are taken away from Warren Sellers Sportfishing to other sites where a variety of cookies may be used. We cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. Social MediaIf you share our content through social media, g us on Facebook,  those social networks will record that you have done so and may set a cookie for this purpose. Warren Sellers Sportfishing does not control any of the content from the social media plugins, and recommend you contact those sites directly for their privacy and data sharing policies.   End of Privacy Policy. Last revision: June 6, 2020.Warren Sellers Sportfishing - chartering since 1974 Phone: 1-626-656-FISH (3474) | Privacy PolicyCarefully crafted in Colorado by Artspark Web Design
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. Privacy Policy AcceptThe cookie settings on this website are set to "allow cookies" to give you the best browsing experience possible. If you continue to use this website without changing your cookie settings or you click "Accept" below then you are consenting to this.Close
